Hi Tinker Hub, this is Indu Joodan, a 3rd
year computer science student from College of Engineering,
Specializing in A and M.
I am someone who enjoys learning by
building, teaching by sharing and growing through communities.
Well, my vision about Tinker Hub is to
give campus a go-to space for students to learn
Beyond their syllabus.
A space where students can learn by
completing tasks, experimentation, asking questions,
As well as building and growing as a
community.
So, the main challenges I have seen is
lack of consistency as well as the hesitation and
Lack of confidence of students.
So, in order to tackle this, I will be
implementing beginner friendly study jams and weekly sessions
Where people can gather together and
contribute their knowledge.
Following this, there will be mechatones
and project building events, which will showcase
Their skill sets and help them learn new
things.
So, talking about myself, I am not a
hardcore tech guy, but hackathons, communities, as well as
Self-learning shapes me.
I have actively participated in a lot of
hackathons, tech events and contributed as a leader as well as a project builder.
Even I have built solo projects as well as
group projects where that improved and gave me more
Knowledge on technology, AI, as well as
leadership and mentorship.
I am currently the student lead of
Entrepreneurship Development Club under IEDC of College of Engineering,
I have organized workshops, even as like
Enigma 25, as well as conducted the local round of Smart India Hackathon.
I am also the secretary of the 4th club
College of Engineering, and an active volunteer of Tinger Hub
College of Engineering, I have
participated in last year's Tinger Hack as the mentor and it was a
Beautiful experience for sharing my
knowledge.
Recently, I have taken a session on the
2-day study jam of Prompt Engineering conducted by Tinger Hub College of Engineering.
So, if you ask me why Tinger Hub is, like
I said, I am also a volunteer of Tinger Hub College of Engineering at Tinger
And it really excited me on seeing how the
community creates an environment for learners to come together and grow together.
So, I really want to contribute my vision
and create an impact on students to pursue their passion by creating an
Environment where learners can come and
grow together and create unique achievements.
So, for me, Tinger Hub represents
curiosity, openness and learning without fear.
Having it on my campus means creating a
culture where students support each other and grow together.
I would love to contribute to building
that space. Thank you for the opportunity.